Videogame High School 1x05 English
Subtitles by: Freddie Wong
ENJOY ALL VOD IN HIGH QUALITY @ 4KVOD.TV
GET LIVE TV,MOVIES,SHOWS IN ONE PACKAGE
http://facebook.com/VideoGameHighSchool
Day of The JV/Varsity Scrimmage Two Hours Remain
Rhythm Method
Huh, you draw in the notes section too?
Oh, I'm just writing a little not to give to Jenny after the scrim.
Not a love note,
or anything like that. I mean, she totally has a boyfriend
who hates me.
Nah, it's more of a
"It's all cool, you know, let's...
let's be friends" sort of note.
Oh. I like to draw extra lines to make it graph paper.
Yo Brian, man. Kick ass out there.
Thanks man.
I will give it my best shot.
Good, cause we have two weeks allowance on you beating The Law.
Alright. Settle down. Settle down people. Settle down.
I am proud to be your TA for rhythm gaming this year
A sport...
of true champions.
Something you two losers in the back could stand to learn something about.
♪ And now, without further ado, ♪
♪ I present to you, the sultan of shred ♪
♪ the prince of pentatonic, ♪
♪ the raddest dad, ♪
♪ with the baddest ad... itude. ♪
Freddie Wong!
My dad!
Sup losers.
Or should I say heroes?
Nope. All losers.
Thats all right. That's why you took this class.
To learn from the best, me,
Freddie Wong. Hero.
Alright. Whew!
First rule of heroism.
Give the people what they want.
See, when you're a hero,
people want to be you.
They want to do you.
They want to be you while they do you.
Oh my god.
Be careful.
Cause if you don't give the people what they want, they'll divorce you,
they'll take your sweet dirt bike,
and they'll leave you with a no good loser for a son.
Yeeha!
Grip the steering wheel of destiny!
Drift.
What are you...?
Nooooooooo!
So, who wants some pizza?
Ted, are you sure you are ok, man? That was, like, really rough.
100% Big D. I just gotta refuel.
Ok. Umm...
Well, I have to get to scrimmage, buddy. But...
Ki can you take care of him for a little while?
I'm on it.
Good luck Brian.
- Alright. - Ya man, don't...
Don't worry about me. Good dad out there.
I mean, good love dad.
Good luck Brian.
See ya.
End of Seventh Period One Hour Remains
Go get 'em Brian.
Break the Law!
Thanks man. Cool slogan.
The Law Vs Brian D Justice will be served
I'll get to everybody, I'll get to everybody. Hold your horses. Calm down.
Hey! Give me twenty big ones on Brian D.
Alright, a risk taker, huh? I like that.
Hey. Speak of the devil.
There you go. Who's next? Who's next?
What ya got? What ya got? I'll take yeah. I'll make your bet for ya.
That's fine with me. What ya want? Ten on Law. There ya go. Boom.
Hey man. Look, I was thinking, maybe you can just do some fancy foot work
or caps lock and run away when you're out there.
Cause I am betting you can make it at least three minutes against The Law.
Say hi to The Law for me, Brian.
No pressure.
The Junior Varsity Pre-Game Meeting - Thirty Minutes Remain -
Ok. Jpop, Rico, Moriarity,
Left Flank is all you.
Jumping Jax!
I want to see those grenade skills in action.
And as for the little freshman that could,
stay tight and out of sight.
Any questions?
Yeah. Isn't this scrimmage just an excuse for your boyfriend to pad his kill reel.
Ya. You're right.
Varsity is out there to show off.
We. We're out there to kick ass.
Stay calm, stick the plan...
and we're gonna wipe the smirk right off their faces.
And as for my boyfriend...
that maggot isn't gonna talk to me for a week after we're through with him!
- Sound good? - Yeah!
Alright. See you on the battlefield. Dismissed.
Hey...
rad speech. I mean...
consider me pumped.
Do you need something?
Nope. I just thought you might want to check this out.
Bam! New DXM, fresh import.
And uh, you might want to check out the notes section. B-t-dubs.
This is...
pretty cool actually.
But I have to stay focused right now.
You should too, Brian.
Yah. No, totally.
Well.
If you ever want to get unfocused...
Hey.
I've seen the posters.
This is team CTF, not a deathmatch.
You follow my orders, you'll be fine.
You got it captain.
Brian's Private Pre-Game Pump Up Five MInutes Remain
Stay frosty B.D.
Jenny wants you to avoid The Law.
Consider it done.
They won't even know I'm there. Ninja style.
He made a whole soda can disappear in my mouth.
Victory burgers after the game?
More like defeateritos.
Defeateritoes with cheese.
Speaking of dead meat, what was Jenny thinking putting BrianD on her team?
She was probably thinking I'm awesome.
Guys, Jenny wasn't thinking,
she was following orders.
Wait. You told her to put him on the team?
Course Cold Turkey.
Cause while I love a well earned victory burg,
what I really love, more than anything,
is to kill...
Brian D.
That big baby Brian is bound to burn, bro.
Nice one Alliterator.
He's going down in flames.
In front of everyone.
And when the smoke clears...
there will be no doubt
that he was anything
but a worthless, no talent fluke.
With cheese.
So uh, lets go.
- Yep! - Alright then!
Oh, Brian...
- What's he doing? - Costing me five hundred bucks!
Get with the program Brian.
Brian, I am going to the intel. Get to that structure and cover me.
You know, I think I will just stick back here and nade spam, sir.
Damnit Brian, what is your malfunction?
Is The Law going to be waiting for me up there?
Follow my orders, or get off my team.
Avenge me.
Damnit, Brian.
Yeah!
Give the people what they want.
Yeah! Come on Brian! Woo!
♪ This song's about The Law!♪
♪ Long Arm's looking for you... ♪
♪ Long Arm of The Law! ♪
- Oh, you're in trouble now! -
- Here it comes! -
♪ Long Arm of The Law! ♪
- Yesss! -
- Clean yourself up! -
- Varsity Wins. -
Performance Analytics Expulsion Threshold
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today